icruise.com 2018-12-25

# Privacy Policy for iCruise.com

Protecting your privacy is important to us. This privacy statement covers iCruise.com and all the websites of WMPH Incorporated ("WMPH," "we," "us," "our"). We hope the following statement will help you understand how WMPH collects, uses, and safeguards the personal information you provide us on our site, via telephone, or via other communication. By accessing or using WMPH's websites and/or services, you agree that you have read, understood, and agree to WMPH's collection, storage, and disclosure of your information as described in this privacy statement.

This privacy statement addresses the following topics: 

  * What personally identifiable information WMPH collects 
  * What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the website 
  * What organization collects the information 
  * How WMPH uses the information 
  * With whom WMPH may share user information 
  * What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information. 
  * How WMPH processes children's information 
  * How WMPH processes information from European Union residents 
  * What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under WMPH control 
  * How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact us at [support@wmph.com](mailto:support@wmph.com?Subject=Questions%20About%20the%20WMPH%20Privacy%20Policy)

## **Information Collection and Use**

**Information Collection**  
WMPH is the sole owner of the information collected on our website. WMPH collects information from our users at several different points on our website, over the telephone, or via other communication from the user.

**Reservations**  
WMPH requests personal information from the user to process travel reservations. A user voluntarily provides contact information (such as name, gender, date of birth, passport information, email address, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customers' reservations. If we have trouble processing a reservation, the information is used to contact the user.

WMPH may share the user's information with third party travel providers in order to fulfill travel reservations. These providers include those with whom the user has requested travel arrangements, such as cruise lines, hotels, airlines, transportation providers, and tour providers. WMPH may also share financial information with banks and payment service providers to process transactions related to a user's travel arrangements.

WMPH does not retain personal information for longer than necessary to fulfill these purposes and in accordance with applicable law.

**Profile**  
We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third parties to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user's visit to our website, and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them. We do not share your profile with other third parties, however, on occasion we may direct market products to you on behalf of our business partners. Your profile is shared in aggregate form only.

**Cookie Policy**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the users computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the users hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.

**Log Files**  
Like most standard website servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. This information may be shared with affiliated third-party entities for purposes of data analysis.

**Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)**  
Our third party advertising companies employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. The main difference between the two is that clear gifs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence.

Clear Gifs can "work with" existing cookies on a computer if they are both from the same website or advertising company. That means, for example, that if a person visited www.companyX.com, which uses an advertising company's clear gif, the website [or advertising company] would match the clear gif's identifier and the advertising company's cookie ID number, to show the past online behavior for that computer. This collected information would then be given to the advertising company [or website].

We do use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by the recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If users would like to opt-out of these emails, please see the Opt-out section.

## **Communications from the Site**

**Special Offers and Updates**  
We will send all new members a welcoming email. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.

**Newsletter**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.

**Service Announcements**  
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.

**Customer Service**  
We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services. In regards to issues relating to their account, we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the user's wishes.

## **Sharing**

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our website.

**Business Transitions**  
In the event WMPH goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

**Choice/Opt-out**  
Our users are given the opportunity to opt-out of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for information. For example, our order form has an opt-out mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists.

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to the mail with "unsubscribe" in the subject line, or email us at [support@wmph.com](mailto:support@wmph.com?Subject=Opt-Out%20Request%20from%20WMPH%20Privacy%20Policy%20Page)

**Links**  
This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

**Chat Rooms, Message Boards, and Public Forums**  
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through e-mail, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

**Child Privacy**  
WMPH collects personal information about children as voluntarily provided by legally-authorized adults for the purpose of processing travel reservations as explained in the Information Collection and Use section. WMPH's websites and services are not targeted at, nor does WMPH knowingly collect personal information from, children under the age of 18. If WMPH has reason to believe that information is being provided by a person under the age of 18, it will not collect the information. Users who believe information has been collected from a person under age 18 may contact WMPH via email at [support@wmph.com](mailto:support@wmph.com?Subject=Child%20Privacy%20Issue%20from%20WMPH%20Privacy%20Policy%20Page) or via the Contact Information below.

**For Users and Customers in the European Union (?EU?)**  
Users and customers residing in the EU are entitled to the following rights regarding the personal information that we collect and hold:

  * _Right of Access:_ The right to obtain access to your personal information. 
  * _Right of Rectification:_ The right to obtain rectification of the user's personal information without undue delay where that personal information in inaccurate or incomplete. 
  * _Right of Erasure:_ The right to obtain erasure of the user's personal information without undue delay in certain circumstances, such as where the personal information is no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which it was collected or processed. 
  * _Right of Restriction:_ The right to obtain the restriction of the processing performed by WMPH on your personal information in certain circumstances, such as where accuracy of the information is contested by the user, for a period enabling WMPH to verify the accuracy of that information. 

In some cases, WMPH's ability to uphold these rights for the user may depend upon WMPH's obligations to process personal information for security, safety, or fraud prevention reasons, compliance with regulatory or legal requirements, or because processing is necessary to deliver the user-requested services. Where this is the case, WMPH will inform the user of specific details in response to a request. To discuss how to exercise these rights, you may contact WMPH via email at [support@wmph.com](mailto:support@wmph.com?Subject=GDPR%20Rights%20Exercise%20from%20WMPH%20Privacy%20Policy%20Page) or via the Contact Information below. Users and customers also have the right to file a complaint with the relevant data protection regulator.

**Security**  
This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, their information is protected both online and off-line.

When our reservation form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our booking form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just surfing.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information offline. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to user information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users' information is protected. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment with our Internet Service Provider.

**Transferring Data**  
WMPH is headquartered in the United States and may have affiliated relationships with service providers in the United States and in other countries. WMPH may need to transfer a user's personal information to other countries for purposes of processing and/or storage, for example, to cruise lines, hotels, or other affiliated travel providers that operate in other countries; to immigration authorities in other countries; and to affiliated data storage entities. For users residing the in EU, such transfers may involve sending personal information to countries outside the EU; such transfers are made pursuant to appropriate safeguards of the data.

**Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information**

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate user's personally identifiable information. This can usually be done by emailing our Customer Support at [support@wmph.com](mailto:support@wmph.com?Subject=User%20Informaton%20Request%20from%20WMPH%20Privacy%20Policy%20Page). Or, contact us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email and by posting a notice on our website for 30 days.

This policy was last updated on May 25, 2018.

**Contact Information**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

  * WMPH Vacations / iCruise.com  
220 Congress Park Drive, Suite 330  
Delray Beach, Florida 33445  
Phone: 1-561-900-9401  
Fax: 1-561-243-0007  
Email: [support@wmph.com](mailto:support@wmph.com?Subject=Questions%20About%20the%20WMPH%20Privacy%20Policy)

**For Cruise Reservations, please call: Toll Free: 1-800-427-8473**

**WMPH Vacations**  
_Building personal and lasting relationships by consistently exceeding expectations._
